<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><!--
  ~ Copyright (C) 2016 The Android Open Source Project
  ~
  ~ Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
  ~ you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
  ~ You may obtain a copy of the License at
  ~
  ~      http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
  ~
  ~ Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
  ~ distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
  ~ WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
  ~ See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
  ~ limitations under the License.
  -->

<resources>
    <string-array name="cake">
        <item>Christmas Cake</item>
        <item>Birthday Cake</item>
        <item>Wedding Cake</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="drinks">
        <item>Ice-cream</item>
        <item>Coffee</item>
        <item>Cocktail</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="indofood">
        <item>Satay</item>
        <item>Fried Rice</item>
        <item>Buntut Soup</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="italian">
        <item> Grilled Pasta</item>
        <item>Pizza</item>
        <item>Torta Rustica</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="foto">

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="des">
        <item>Torta Rustica is  a delecius pie best eaten cooled to room temperature, perhaps on a nice
        picnic with some salad or boiled potatoes.</item>
        <item>Birthday cake is a cake that served to someone in her/his birthday.</item>
        <item>Christmas cake is a cake that served in christmas day. This cake usually served when
        a big family get together.</item>
        <item>Coffee is people's favorite drink. In the world, there is so many kind of coffee, especially
        in Indonesia.</item>
        <item>Ice-cream is sweetened frozen food typically eaten as a snack or dessert.</item>
        <item>Wedding cake is a cake that usually used in wedding party. </item>
        <item>Cocktail is a mixed drink typically made with a distilled beverage that is mixed with other
        ingredients</item>
        <item>Satay is made of cube meat that are skewered in kebab style, then grilled and eaten
        with a peanut sauce dip.</item>
        <item>Fried rice is a tasty dish that made from steamed rice stir-fried in a wok </item>
        <item>Buntut soup is one of kind Indonesia food that made from slice of meat.</item>
        <item>Pasta is staple food of traditional Italian cuisine, with the first reference dating to
        1154 in sicily.</item>
        <item>Pizza is a flatbread generally topped with tomato sauce and cheese and baked ina oven </item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="bahan">
        <item>2(8 ounce) containers candied cherries
        1 (8 ounce) container candied mixed citrus peel
        2 cups raisins
        1 cup dried currants
        1 cup dates, pitted and chopped
        1 (2.25 ounce) packages blanched silvered almonds
        1/2 cup brandy
        1/2 cup all-purpose flour
        2 cups all-purpose flour
        1/2 teaspoon baking soda
        1 teaspoon ground cloves
        1 teaspoon ground allspice
        1 teaspoon ground cinnamon
        1/2 teaspoon salt
        1 cup butter
        2 cups packed brown sugar
        6 eggs
        3/4 cup molasses
        3/4 cup apple juice</item>
        <item>
            1,5 cups butter
            2 1/3 cups confectioners' sugar
            7 egg yolks
            4,5 cups cake flour
            3/4 teaspoon salt
            2,5 teaspoon baking powder
            1 3/4 cups milk
            1,5 teaspoon vanilla extract
        </item>
        <item>
            3 tablespoons soy sauce
            3 tablespoons tomato sauce
            1 tablespoon peanut oil
            2 clover garlic, peeled and minced
            1 pinch ground black pepper
            1 pinch ground cumin
            6 skinless, boneless chicken breast halves-cubed
            1 tablespoon vegetable oil
            1/4 cup minced onion
            1 clove garlic, peeled and minced
            1 cup water
            1/2 cup chunky peanut butter
            2 tablespoons soy sauce
            2 tablespoons white sugar
            1 tablespoon lemon juice
            skewers
        </item>
        <item>
            1 cup uncooked white rice
            2 cups water
            cooking spray
            3 eggs, beaten
            1 tablespoon vegetable oil
            1 onion, chopped
            1 leek, chopped
            1 clove garlic, minced
            2 green chile peppers, chooped
            1/2 pound skinless, boneless chicken breasts, cut into thin strips
            1/2 pound peeled and deveined prawns
            1 teaspoon ground coriander
            1 teaspoon ground cumin
            3 tablespoon sweet soy sauce
        </item>
        <item>
            1,5 fliud ounces light rum
            1 fliud ounce lime juice
            1 teaspoon simple syrup
            1 cup ice
        </item>
        <item>
            4 shallots, peeled and halved
            1 large onion, quartered, divided
            1 (2 inch) pice ginger, peeled and thinly slice across the grain
            5 cloves garlic, peeled
            3 tablespoon canola oil
            6 whole cloves (optional)
            1/2 teaspoon ground nutmeg
            1/4 teaspoon groun cinnamon
            4 pound meaty oxtail pieces, at room temperature
            2 large carrots, cut into 2-inch pieces
            3 stalks celery,, cut into 1-inch pieces
            water to cover
            2 teaspoon salt
            1/2 teaspoon ground black pepper
            3 waxy potatoes, scrubbed and cut into 1,5 inch chunks
            3 large carrots, cut into 2-inch pieces
            2 tablespoon white sugar
            2 tablespoon fish sauce
            3 ripe roma tomatoes, slice horizontally into 1/2 inch wedges
            1 (2.8 ounce) can french-fried onions
        </item>
        <item>
            3/4 cup sugar
            1 cup milk
            1/4 teaspoon salt
            2 tablespoon unsweetened cocoa powder
            3 egg yolk, lightly beaten
            2 ounces smisweet chocolate, chopped
            2 cups heavy cream
            1 teaspoon vanilla extract
        </item>
        <item>
            1 cup butter, softened
            3 cup white sugar
            7 eggs
            1 tablespoon vanilla extract
            3 cups all-purpose flour
            1/4 teaspoon baking powder
            1/4 teaspoon baking soda
            1 cup sour cream
        </item>
        <item>
            2 tablespoons sweetened condensed milk, or more to taste
            2/3 cup strong brewed coffee
            1 teaspoon non-diary creamer (such as coffee-mate), or more to taste
            1 teaspoon hot cocoa mix (such as godiva) or more to taste (optional)
        </item>
        <item>
            1/3 cup olive oil
            2 tablespoon red wine vinegar
            1 teaspoon dried oregano
            salt and pepper, chopped
            1 green bell pepper, chopped
            2 cloves gerlic, minced
            2 carrots
            1.5 cups broccoli florets, lightly steamed or blanched
            4 cups uncooked rotni pasta
        </item>
        <item>
            3.5 cups all-purpose flour, or as needed
            1 envelope Fleischmann's Pizaa Crust Yeast
            1 tablespoon sugar
            1,5 teaspoon salt
            1 1/3 cup oil
            Additional flour for rolling
            Additional oil for grilling
            Pizza sauce
            Other toppings as desired
            Shredded mozzarella cheese
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="cara">
        <item>
            1. Start charcoal fire or preheat gas grill to medium-high heat
            2. Combine 2 cups flour, undissolved yeast, sugar and salt in a large bowl.
                Add very warm water and oil; mix until well blended, about 1 minute. Gradually add enough
                flour ro make a soft dough. Dough should form a ball and will be slightly sticky.
                Knead** on a floured surface, adding additional flour if necessary, until smooth
                and elastic but no sticky, about 5 minutes.
            3. Divide dough into 8 portions. Pat or roll dough on a well-floured counter to about
                8 inch circles; they do not need to be perfect
            4. Brush both sides of crust with additional oil. Using hands, lift each crust carefully
                and place on grill. Cook for 3 to 4 minutes until bottom is lightly browned and top looks set.
                Using ong handled tongs, remove crust from grill, grilled side up, to a platter or baking sheet
            5. Lightly add sauce and top grilled side of each pizza crust. Excess sauce or toppings
                make the pizza hard to handle. Repeat with remaining pizzas.
            6. Carefully slide each pizza onto the grill. Cook an additional 3 o 4 minutes until
                bottom of crust is browned and cheese is melted. Remove from grill and serve immediately
        </item>
        <item>
            1. Mix together the oil, vinegar, basil, oregano, salt, and pepper. Set aside
            2. Bring large pot of salted water to boil; add rotini and bring to a boil again.
                Cook until rotini is al dente;drain well. Return the rotini to the pot.
            3. While rotini cooking heat oil in a fring pan and saute red bell papper, green bell pepper,
                garlic and carrots. Cook until vegetables are softened. Place the broccoli in the frying
                pan and cook another 2 minutes
            4. Pour the cooked vegetables into the pot with he pasta. Pour the vinaigrette over the pasta and
                vegetables. Toss to distribute vegetables and vinaigrette evenly.
        </item>
        <item>
            1. Pour some boiling water in a glass. Let sit to warm the glass, about 1 minute. Pour
                out water
            2. Pour condensed milk into the warmed glass. Top with coffee. Stir in creamer and
                hot cocoa mix
        </item>
        <item>
            1. Preheat oven to 325 degrees F (165 degrees C). Grease and flour a 9x13 inch pan
                or a 10 inch Bunt pan
            2. In a large bowl, cream together the butter and sugar. Beat in the eggs, one at a time, mixing well
                after each. Then stir in the vanilla. Combine the flour, baking soda and baking powder, add to the
                creamed mixture and mix until all of the flour is absorbed. Finally, stir in the sour cream. Mix for 1
                or 2 minutes just to be sure there are no lumps. Pour the bater into the prepared pan.
            3. Bake in the preheated oven for 45 to 60 minute, or until a toothpick inserted into the of cake comes out
                clean. For Bunt cakes, allow the cake to cool in the pan for 10 minutes before inverting onto a wire rack
        </item>
        <item>
            1. Combine sugar, milk, salt, and cocoa powder in a saucepan over medium heat, stirring constantly.
                Bring to a simmer. Place the egg yolks into a small bowl. Gradually stir in about 1/2 cup of the
                hot liquid, and return to the saucepan. Heat until thickened, but do not boil. Remove from the heat, and stir
                in the chopped chocolate until chocolate is melted. Pour into a chilled bowl, and refrigerate for
                about 2 hours until cold, stirring occasionally
            2. When chocolate mixture has complete cooled, stir in the cream and vanilla. Pour into an ice cream maker, and freeze
                according to manufacturer's directions
        </item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
